Guide to the National Education Association-Commissions records, 1918-1982 NEA1002.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Commission on Professional Rights and Responsibilities, 1922-1981; Series 2; 82.75 Linear Feet
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Charges, 1967-1969; Series 2 (Box 887, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Communications about the Investigation, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 887, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Correspondence [file 1/4], 1967-1970; Series 2 (Box 888, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Correspondence [file 2/4], 1967-1970; Series 2 (Box 888, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Correspondence [file 3/4], 1967-1970; Series 2 (Box 888, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Correspondence [file 4/4], 1967-1970; Series 2 (Box 888, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Dekalb Education Association, 1963-1966; Series 2 (Box 888, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Dekalb Education Association, 1965-1968; Series 2 (Box 888, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-"The Dekalb School Study", May 1963-October 1978; Series 2 (Box 889, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Executive Committee Hearing, 1965-1968; Series 2 (Box 889, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Exhibits [file 1/4], 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 889, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Exhibits [file 2/4], 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 889, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Exhibits [file 3/4], 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 889, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Exhibits [file 4/4], 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 889, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Grand Jury Appearance, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 889, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Handbook for School Administration, July 1967; Series 2 (Box 890, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Investigation Notes and Outlines, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 890, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Newspaper Clippings [file 1/2], 1967-1969; Series 2 (Box 890, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Newspaper Clippings [file 2/2], 1967-1969; Series 2 (Box 890, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Notebook, circa 1967; Series 2 (Box 890, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Photos, November 1967; Series 2 (Box 890, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Preliminary Inquiry, 1967-1978; Series 2 (Box 890, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Press Clippings, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 891, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Procedural Documentation [file 1/2], 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 891, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Procedural Documentation [file 2/2], 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 891, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-References, Footnotes, Quoted Statements, and Documents, 1965-1967; Series 2 (Box 891, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Request for Investigation, 1964-1968; Series 2 (Box 891, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-School System Data, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 891, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Sechler Documents, 1965; Series 2 (Box 892, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Special Committee, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 892, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Substantive Documentation [file 1/2], 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 892, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Dekalb County-Substantive Documentation [file 2/2], 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 892, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Georgia-Milledgeville #251, January 1967; Series 2 (Box 892, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Guam-Agana #228, 1966; Series 2 (Box 892, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Hawaii-Honolulu #121, 1964-1965; Series 2 (Box 892, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Hawaii-Honolulu #224, 1966; Series 2 (Box 893, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Idaho [file 1/2], 1964-1965; Series 2 (Box 1519, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Idaho [file 2/2], 1964-1965; Series 2 (Box 1519, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Jefferson County-Aftermath, 1964; Series 2 (Box 893, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-About Report, 1965; Series 2 (Box 893, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-Case, 1963-1964; Series 2 (Box 893, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-Clippings, 1963-1964; Series 2 (Box 893, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-Documents, 1964; Series 2 (Box 893, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-Draft (December 8, 1964), Series 2 (Box 893, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-Drafts, 1964; Series 2 (Box 893, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-Follow-Up #253, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 894, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-General File, 1963-1965; Series 2 (Box 894, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-Idaho Education Association, 1963-1965; Series 2 (Box 894, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-Leavenworth Study, 1961-1962; Series 2 (Box 894, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-Material, March 1963-October 1964; Series 2 (Box 894, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-Notes, 1962-1963; Series 2 (Box 895, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-Press Releases, 1964-1965; Series 2 (Box 895, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-Report, circa 1964; Series 2 (Box 895, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-School Visitations and Committee Orientations, 1964; Series 2 (Box 895, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-Special Committee, 1964-1965; Series 2 (Box 895, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-"A State-Wide Study of Educational Conditions and School Finance", January 1965; Series 2 (Box 895, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Statewide-Statistical Data, 1962-1964; Series 2 (Box 895, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Twin Falls-Aftermath, 1950-1951; Series 2 (Box 895, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Idaho-Twin Falls-Summary, 1950-1961; Series 2 (Box 895, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Bloomington, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 896, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Champaign, 1970; Series 2 (Box 896, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Chicago #205, 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 896, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Chicago-Abridgement, 1945-1960; Series 2 (Box 896, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Chicago-Aftermath [file 1/2], 1939-1963; Series 2 (Box 896, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Chicago-Aftermath [file 2/2], 1939-1963; Series 2 (Box 896, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Chicago-Malcolm X College [file 1/2], 1972-1973; Series 2 (Box 896, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Chicago-Malcolm X College [file 2/2], 1972-1973; Series 2 (Box 897, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Cook County, 1970; Series 2 (Box 897, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Decatur #236 [file 1/2], 1966-1969; Series 2 (Box 897, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Decatur #236 [file 2/2], 1966-1969; Series 2 (Box 897, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Evanston [file 1/2], 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 898, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Evanston [file 2/2], 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 898, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Evanston-Coffin, Gregory C., 1969; Series 2 (Box 898, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Evanston-Correspondence [file 1/2], 1969-1971; Series 2 (Box 898, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Evanston-Correspondence [file 2/2], 1969-1971; Series 2 (Box 898, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Evanston-Documents, 1965-1969; Series 2 (Box 898, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Evanston-NEA Actions, 1969; Series 2 (Box 899, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Evanston-Newspaper Articles, 1969; Series 2 (Box 899, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Evanston-School District Records, 1969; Series 2 (Box 899, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Harlem #284, 1968; Series 2 (Box 899, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Harvey #214, 1966; Series 2 (Box 899, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Joliet #239, 1966; Series 2 (Box 899, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Macomb #16, 1962-1964; Series 2 (Box 900, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Oglesby, 1951-1965; Series 2 (Box 900, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Peoria #242 [file 1/2], 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 900, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Peoria #242 [file 2/2], 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 900, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Rockford #156, 1965; Series 2 (Box 900, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Rockford #258, 1967; Series 2 (Box 900, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Illinois-Urbana #328, 1970; Series 2 (Box 900, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Elkhart #190, 1965; Series 2 (Box 900, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Fayette County, 1973; Series 2 (Box 901, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Fort Wayne [file 1/2], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 901, Folder 2)
    Contained an audio cassette tape, "Indiana-Statement", which has been removed and placed in the Media Materials subseries.
  - Investigations-Indiana-Fort Wayne [file 2/2], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 901, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Fort Wayne #231 [file 1/2], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 901, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Fort Wayne #231 [file 2/2], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 902, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Fort Wayne-First Draft, December 1966; Series 2 (Box 902, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Fort Wayne-Fourth Draft [file 1/2], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 902, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Fort Wayne-Fourth Draft [file 2/2], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 902, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Fort Wayne-Second Draft, January 1967; Series 2 (Box 902, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Fort Wayne-Special Committee, 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 902, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Fort Wayne-Third Draft, April 1967; Series 2 (Box 902, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Gary #99, 1964; Series 2 (Box 902, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Gary-Aftermath, 1964; Series 2 (Box 903, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Gary-Clippings, 1964; Series 2 (Box 903, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Indianapolis, 1960; Series 2 (Box 903, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Indianapolis #191, 1965-1967; Series 2 (Box 903, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Ligonier #197, 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 903, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Indiana-Statewide-Financial Study [file 1/2], 1971; Series 2 (Box 903, Folder 6)
    Included "Financing of the Public Elementary and Secondary Schools of Indiana", by the Indiana Commission on State Tax and Financing Policy, 1970; "Measuring the Fiscal Capacity and Effort of State and Local Areas", by the Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, March 1971; "1967 Census of Governments, Indiana", by the U.S. Department of Commerce, 1967; and "1967 Census of Governments, Compendium of Government Finances", by the U.S. Department of Commerce, 1967.
  - Investigations-Indiana-Statewide-Financial Study [file 2/2], 1971; Series 2 (Box 903, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Information Sheets, circa 1971; Series 2 (Box 903, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Iowa-Clinton #145, 1964; Series 2 (Box 903, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Iowa-Pleasantville, 1964; Series 2 (Box 903, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-Iowa-Sioux Falls, 1972; Series 2 (Box 903, Folder 11)
  - Investigations-Iowa-State Professional Rights and Responsibilities Committee Hearing, 1968; Series 2 (Box 903, Folder 12)
  - Investigations-Iowa-State University, 1972; Series 2 (Box 903, Folder 13)
  - Investigations-Kansas-El Dorado #105, 1964-1965; Series 2 (Box 904, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Kansas-Haysville #207, 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 904, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Kansas-Leavenworth, 1962-1965; Series 2 (Box 904, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Kansas-Statewide #257 [file 1/2], 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 904, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Kansas-Statewide #257 [file 2/2], 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 904, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Kansas-Statewide-Background of Study and Summary of Committee Observation, 1967; Series 2 (Box 904, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Kansas-Statewide-Newspaper Clippings, 1967; Series 2 (Box 904, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Kansas-Statewide-"Report of a Public School Study, Kansas, A State-Wide Study of Educational Conditions and Financial Support", November 1967; Series 2 (Box 905, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Kansas-Statewide-Special Committee, 1967; Series 2 (Box 905, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Kansas-Wichita #288, 1968; Series 2 (Box 905, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Aftermath, 1963-1965; Series 2 (Box 905, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Clippings, 1962; Series 2 (Box 905, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Comments, 1963; Series 2 (Box 905, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Distribution, 1963; Series 2 (Box 905, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Dittos, 1962; Series 2 (Box 905, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Documents [file 1/2], 1961-1962; Series 2 (Box 906, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Documents [file 2/2], 1961-1962; Series 2 (Box 906, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Draft as Revised at Special Committee Meeting, 1962; Series 2 (Box 906, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Events Since the Investigation, 1962; Series 2 (Box 906, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Expulsion Hearings Transcript, January 1964; Series 2 (Box 906, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Final Appeals, 1962-1963; Series 2 (Box 906, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Galley Proofs, 1963; Series 2 (Box 907, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Legal Action, 1960-1962; Series 2 (Box 907, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Material from Earl Bellew, 1947; Series 2 (Box 907, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Material Presented by Assistant Superintendent of Schools, 1962-1965; Series 2 (Box 907, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Notes (BAB), circa 1962; Series 2 (Box 907, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Notes (RLM), circa 1962; Series 2 (Box 907, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Page Proofs, 1963; Series 2 (Box 907, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Preliminary Statements, 1961-1962; Series 2 (Box 907, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Press Schedules, 1963; Series 2 (Box 907, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Special Committee, 1962-1963; Series 2 (Box 907, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Special Committee Initial Reactions, 1962; Series 2 (Box 907, Folder 11)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Carter County-Study, June 1962; Series 2 (Box 907, Folder 12)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Elkhorn City #287, 1968; Series 2 (Box 908, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Jefferson County, 1972; Series 2 (Box 908, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Louisville, 1965; Series 2 (Box 1519, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Louisville #102, 1964-1966; Series 2 (Box 908, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Louisville-Clippings, 1964-1966; Series 2 (Box 908, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Louisville-Distribution and Release, 1965; Series 2 (Box 1002, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Louisville-First Draft, March 1965; Series 2 (Box 908, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Louisville-Notes, 1965; Series 2 (Box 908, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Louisville-Press Releases, 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 908, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Louisville-Special Committee, 1964-1965; Series 2 (Box 908, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-McCracken County #282, 1967-1968; Series 2 (Box 909, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Oldham County, 1969; Series 2 (Box 909, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Pike County, 1969; Series 2 (Box 909, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Pikeville #238 [file 1/2], 1967-1972; Series 2 (Box 909, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Pikeville #238 [file 2/2], 1967-1972; Series 2 (Box 909, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Pikeville-"The Campaign", 1964-1967; Series 2 (Box 909, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Pikeville-"Day in Court", 1966; Series 2 (Box 909, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Pikeville-News Clippings, 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 909, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Pikeville-Special Meeting of PCEA, October 1966; Series 2 (Box 910, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Alternate Tax Sources, 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 910, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Appalachia, 1965-1970; Series 2 (Box 910, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Appropriations and Revenue Meeting [file 1/2], November 1970; Series 2 (Box 910, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Appropriations and Revenue Meeting [file 2/2], November 1970; Series 2 (Box 910, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Assessor's Information, 1970; Series 2 (Box 910, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Clippings [file 1/3], 1970; Series 2 (Box 910, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Clippings [file 2/3], 1970; Series 2 (Box 911, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Clippings [file 3/3], 1970; Series 2 (Box 911, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Coal-Appalachia, 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 911, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Commission Ballots and Legal Clearance on Report, 1971; Series 2 (Box 911, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Correspondence-KEA, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 911, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Correspondence-Legislators or LRC, 1970; Series 2 (Box 911, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Correspondence-Miscellaneous, 1970; Series 2 (Box 911, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Correspondence-With Respondents [file 1/2], 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 911, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Correspondence-With Respondents [file 2/2], 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 912, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Documents [file 1/2], 1970; Series 2 (Box 912, Folder 2)
    Included "Duties of Elected County Officials", by the Kentucky Legislative Research Commission, September 1970; "Kentucky Department of Revenue, Annual Report, 1968-1969", December 1969; "Kentucky State Aid and the Educationally Disadvantaged Child", by Michael David Alexander, September 1969; "Beyond the Minimum, a New Dimension for Kentucky's Foundation Program for Education", Kentucky Education Association, January 1967; "Report of Superintendent of Public Instruction", by Wendell P. Butler, June 1969; "Profiles of Kentucky Public Schools", by Kentucky Department of Education, June 1970.
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Documents [file 2/2], 1970; Series 2 (Box 912, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Exhibits [file 1/7], 1970; Series 2 (Box 912, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Exhibits [file 2/7], 1970; Series 2 (Box 912, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Exhibits [file 3/7], 1970; Series 2 (Box 913, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Exhibits [file 4/7], 1970; Series 2 (Box 913, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Exhibits [file 5/7], 1970; Series 2 (Box 913, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Exhibits [file 6/7], 1970; Series 2 (Box 913, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Exhibits [file 7/7], 1970; Series 2 (Box 914, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Follow-up, 1971-1972; Series 2 (Box 914, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-KEA Agenda, 1970; Series 2 (Box 914, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Miscellaneous Hearing Statements, 1970; Series 2 (Box 914, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Preliminary Inquiry, 1970; Series 2 (Box 914, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Professional Negotiation, 1969-1971; Series 2 (Box 914, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Property Assessment and Rates, 1967-1969; Series 2 (Box 914, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-School Visits-Team 1, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 914, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-School Visits-Team 2, 1970; Series 2 (Box 914, Folder 9)
    Contains 9 photos.
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-School Visits-Team 3, 1970; Series 2 (Box 915, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-School Visits-Team 4, 1970; Series 2 (Box 915, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-School Visits-Team 6, 1970-1972; Series 2 (Box 915, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Special Investigating Committee, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 915, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Kentucky-Statewide-Statements from State Department of Public Instruction, 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 915, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-List of Investigations, 1944-1967; Series 2 (Box 915, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Louisiana-Leesville #178, 1963-1965; Series 2 (Box 915, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Louisiana-Louisiana/Mississippi Handbooks, 1970; Series 2 (Box 915, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Louisiana-Louisiana/Mississippi Reports [file 1/4], 1970; Series 2 (Box 915, Folder 9)
    Contained a reel-to-reel audiotape entitled "NEA Task Force in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, March 1970". It has been removed and placed within the media materials series.
  - Investigations-Louisiana-Louisiana/Mississippi Reports [file 2/4], 1970; Series 2 (Box 915, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-Louisiana-Louisiana/Mississippi Reports [file 3/4], 1970; Series 2 (Box 916, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Louisiana-Louisiana/Mississippi Reports [file 4/4], 1970; Series 2 (Box 916, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Louisiana-Louisiana/Mississippi Task Force on Desegregation [file 1/2], 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 916, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Louisiana-Louisiana/Mississippi Task Force on Desegregation [file 2/2], 1970-1971; Series 2 (Box 916, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Louisiana-New Orleans #208, 1966; Series 2 (Box 916, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Louisiana-Plaquemines Parish #301, 1969; Series 2 (Box 916, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Louisiana-Task Force [file 1/2], 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 916, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Louisiana-Task Force [file 2/2], 1969-1970; Series 2 (Box 916, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Maine-Augusta #213, 1966; Series 2 (Box 917, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Maine-Gorham, 1964; Series 2 (Box 917, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Maine-Portland #271 [file 1/2], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 917, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Maine-Portland #271 [file 2/2], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 917, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Aberdeen, 1964; Series 2 (Box 917, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-#217 [file 1/2], 1966-1970; Series 2 (Box 918, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-#217 [file 2/2], 1966-1970; Series 2 (Box 918, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-NEA to Resume Probe, September 1966; Series 2 (Box 1002, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-Newspaper Clippings [file 1/3], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 918, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-Newspaper Clippings [file 2/3], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 918, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-Newspaper Clippings [file 3/3], 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 919, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-Opening Teachers, circa 1966; Series 2 (Box 919, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-Otis Robertson, 1965-1970; Series 2 (Box 917, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Maryland-Baltimore-Pictures, 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 919, Folder 3)
    Contains 37 photos and 19 negatives.